A Guide to the Papers of Murrell Edmunds, 1958-1962
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Murrell Edmunds 1958-1962
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
5989-r
This collection consists of 11 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift of Murrell Edmunds on 20 March 1964.
Contents List
- "December-1958" (poem) [1958], Holograph signed. 1 p.
- Kyle Crichton to Thomas Yoseloff 1960 October 3, TLS. 1 p. (concerning Moon of My Delight)
- Harnett T. Kane 1960 October 21, TLS. 1 p. (concerning Moon of My Delight)
- Stringfellow Barr to Thomas Yoseloff 1960 October 25, ALS. 1 p. (concerning Moon of My Delight)
- Thomas Sancton to Thomas Yoseloff 1960 November 1, TLS. 1 p. (concerning Moon of My Delight)
- Thomas Sancton to Langston Hughes 1960 November 1, TLS (photocopy)
- John Langdon to Murrell Edmunds 1960 November 23, TLS. 1 p. (concerning Moon of My Delight)
- Murrell Edmunds to "Four Little Girls and Their Parents." 1960 November 23, TLS (typewritten transcript)
- (2 printings) cut from Soloho News, 1960 March 18 and Lynchburg News, 1960 [ ca. March 20] [1960], Article on Spring
- "Elegy On A Hillside" (poem) [1962], typescript with autograph changes. 1 p.
- "Elegy On A Hillside" (poem) [1962], typescript. 1 p.